Soomin Lee



in www.linkedin.com/in/soomin-lee-ta



soominlee0522@gmail.com



https://entwistle-905.github.io/Portfolio 2023/



Cornwall, ON



+1) 613-363-9415

Technical Skills

3D Modeling

- 3DS MAX
- ZBrush
- Substance Painter
- Houdini
- > Created buildings, furniture, props and characters.

Technical Art

- Lighting
- Shaders
- Procedural Generation
- VFX (Niagara)
- ➤ Learning technical arts with programming knowledges.

Game Development

- C++, Python
- Unreal Engine 5
- Unity
- > Created games with C++, SDL, and game engines in the college.

Communication

Taking on a leadership role in the capstone project, discussing ideas, communicating with other teammates for the project as a graphic artist and programmer.

Teamwork

> Participated in Game Jam as a Level Designer, VFX Artist, worked with a programmer.

Summary

Creative and passionate technical artist interested in procedural modeling and generation. Experienced in environment design and modeling, and passionate about procedural props modeling, UI design, VFX and pixel art. Collaborative team player with a strong understanding of the game development process. Having extensive applicable education and relevant industry experiences.

Experience

Environment Artist GnC Solution

Oct 2021 - Mar 2022 Seoul, South Korea

- Made 3D models of office structure and furniture, put them in Unreal Engine 4, and worked with other coworkers to make a virtual office for meeting.
- Created 3D characters and environment models, placed them in Unreal Engine 4 and worked with other coworker to make a virtual market for retailers.

3D Artist National University of Cultural Heritage

Sept 2020 – Feb 2021 Buyeo, South Korea

- Fixed historical artifact models scanned by 3D Scanner and made textures from photos with ZBrush and Photoshop.
- Provided completed 3D models and textures and rendering files to the heritage conservation service of the graduate school.

Education

Game Programming Diploma St. Lawrence College

Sept 2022 - April 2024 Cornwall, ON

Bachelor of Conservation Science

Mar 2017 - Feb 2022

Buveo, Korea

Korea National University of Cultural Heritage